(Raj:)under those pretty
rubber gloves?
(Isabella:)No, not for many years.
(Raj:)Oh, so, you are unencumbered?
(Isabella:)Just me and my son.
(Raj:)I love kids,
how old is he?
(Isabella:)Nineteen.
(Raj:)That's a cute age.
(Raj:)They can do so many things.
(Isabella:)He's studying to be
(Isabella:)a lawyer at UCLA.
(Raj:)That's wonderful.
(Raj:)A lawyer, my sister's a lawyer.
(Bernadette:)Look at that,
we have something in common.
(Isabella:)Yeah, I guess we do.
(Raj:)Maybe there are other things
we have in common.
C-Come dinnertime,
do you enjoy eating food?
Ay, Rajesh,
(Isabella:)I think you're very sweet,
but
(Isabella:)I work two jobs and I don't
have time for dating.
(Raj:)Yeah, sure. I understand.
(Raj:)Yeah, I'm very busy, too.
(Isabella:)Oh, please don't take it
personal,
(Isabella:)I think you're a very nice man.
(Raj:)I think you're very nice
as well.
(Isabella:)Thank you for helping me.
(Isabella:)Good night, Rajesh.